

CARLOS GUSTAVO LOPEZ

Front-End Developer

carlos@carlosglopez.com
(305) 987-4508
1701 Gurtler Ct. #2 Orlando, FI 32804

ABOUT ME

I'm a creative front-end developer based in Orlando, FL. I specialize in developing responsive highly interactive websites & web apps with latest technologies such as Bootstrap and PhoneGap. I am passionate about great design and achieving the best user experience by meaningful transitions and color/shape combinations. I am very particular about Maintainability and Modularity with special focus on details.

My professional experience includes more than 4 years working with companies in USA and Canada, such as Disney, Lockheed Martin, Spaceport America, Martin & Vleminckx, and many others.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript, HTMLS, CSS3, Sass, Ruby, PHP

Frameworks & Libraries: Bootstrap, Angular, Node PhoneGap, jQuery (+Mobile, UI), Foundation, GSAP

Tools & Platforms: Github, Scrumwise, Photoshop, Scout, Adobe Edge, Illustrator

Content Management Systems: WordPress, Joomla, Drupal, SharePoint

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Web Developer @IDEAS

NOV 2012 - PRESENT

Worked with an experience design and media production company helping them with web and mobile development services with clients ranging from healthcare, government, enterprise, and entertainment industries worldwide.



Software Engineer @VGlobalTech

NOV 2012 - MAR 2013

Aided with Joomla development to provide clients from various start up companies in the UCF business incubator a managable website. Frequently worked with SEO optomization and keyword researching.



Assistant Technician @IntelligentHearingSystems

MAY 2007 - MAY 2009

Put together SmartCarts and installed software for each system in preparation of shipping and assembled fiber optics cables,

EDUCATION

BA @ University of Central Florida

Digital Media: Web Design Graduated in 2013. Minored in Applied Information Technology

PROJECTS

Disney Catered Events @ IDEAS

Developed a website in WordPress for the client to showcase catering events inside Disney property. www.disneycateredevents.com

InsideLM @ Lockheed Martin

Aided with the migration of Lockheed Martin main internal communications websites into a new Drupal management system,